{"1": {"question": "What is the chamber music for strings set work?", "correct": "1st movement from the String Quartet in G Major K.387 'Spring'", "incorrect": ["1st movement from the String Quartet in G Major K.378 'Summer'", "1st movement from the String Quintet in G Major K.387 'Spring'", "1st movement from the String Quartet in G Minor K.378 'Autumn'"]}, "2": {"question": "Who wrote the chamber music for strings set work?", "correct": "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart", "incorrect": ["Schubert", "Bach", "Beethoven"]}, "3": {"question": "What is the form of the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "Sonata form", "incorrect": ["Binary form", "Ternary form", "Rondo form"]}, "4": {"question": "What is the instrumentation of the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "2 violins, 1 viola, 1 cello", "incorrect": ["1 violin, 1 viola, 1 cello, 1 double bass", "3 violins, 1 viola", "2 violins, 2 violas"]}, "5": {"question": "How many movements are in the full piece of the Mozart?", "correct": "Four", "incorrect": ["Three", "Five", "Ten"]}, "6": {"question": "What key is the first movement in for the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "G major", "incorrect": ["D major", "G minor", "C major"]}, "7": {"question": "Briefly describe the phrasing in the Mozart first movement.", "correct": "The phrases are short and balanced (andecedent and consequent, or question and answer)", "incorrect": ["The phrases are long and smooth. Each phrase brings in a new idea.", "The phrases are unbalanced.", "The phrasing varies greatly, so there is no real way to define it."]}, "8": {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a compositional technique found in the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "Diatonic melodies", "incorrect": ["Recurring rhythmic motifs", "Imitation", "Chromaticism"]}, "9": {"question": "What is a string quartet?", "correct": "A genre of chamber music written for four string instruments", "incorrect": ["A genre of Baroque music written for four string instruments", "A subgenre of K-pop inspired by BTS written for four string instruments", "A genre of Classical music written for four orchestral instruments"]}, "10": {"question": "What separates mid-eighteenth century string quartets from Baroque forms?", "correct": "The lack of a basso continuo part", "incorrect": ["The lack of a second violin part", "The featuring of Jungkook", "Six movements in a quartet"]}, "11": {"question": "What kind of people did the string quartet appeal to?", "correct": "Eighteenth-century upper classes", "incorrect": ["Eighteenth-century working classes", "Nineteenth century upper classes", "BTS fangirls"]}, "12": {"question": "The string quartet was a ready form of private entertainment for whom?", "correct": "Wealthy individuals and families", "incorrect": ["Working-class individuals and families", "Bangtan Sonyeondan", "A large audience"]}, "13": {"question": "Why did composers manipulate conventions of string quartet form for their audiences?", "correct": "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper classes) enjoyed musical literacy and were educated on the form, so manipulating conventions surprised and delighted them.", "incorrect": ["Because President Namjoon asked them to", "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper and middle classes) enjoyed hearing the slight tweaks in convention, as it made it much more interesting for them to listen to.", "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper classes) did not enjoy hearing differences from convention, and the composers liked to annoy them."]}, "14": {"question": "How many string quartets are in the complete set of the Mozart?", "correct": "Six", "incorrect": ["Ten", "Five", "Four", "24?"]}, "15": {"question": "Who did Mozart dedicate the set of string quartets to?", "correct": "Haydn", "incorrect": ["Yoongi", "Purcell", "Bach"]}, "16": {"question": "Which of Haydn's quartets inspired Mozart to write his Haydn Quartets?", "correct": "Haydn's Op.33 set, which Mozart studied closely", "incorrect": ["Haydn's Op.44 set, which Mozart studied closely", "Haydn's Op.22 set, which Mozart studied closely", "Haydn's Op.55 set dedicated to Seokjin"]}, "17": {"question": "When did Haydn hear the quartets that Mozart dedicated to him?", "correct": "1785", "incorrect": ["1995", "1795", "1775"]}, "18": {"question": "What did Haydn say to the father Leopold when he was visiting from Salzburg?", "correct": "Before God, as an honest man, I tell you that your son is the greatest composer known to me either in person or by name. He has taste, and, what is more, the profound knowledge of composition.'", "incorrect": ["BTS is the greatest band ever to form. Their music is wonderfully splendid and your son Wolfgang is quite a horrible composer compared to them.'", "I very much dislike the quartets that your son wrote in my name. They do not reflect my compositions at all. Rather, they are written much more in your son's style than mine.'", "Before God, as an honest man, your son will continue to be the great composer that he is and always has been. His quartets profoundly reflect mine with his own tasteful additions.'"]}, "19": {"question": "What is the Italian term used to indicate bowing on or near the bridge?", "correct": "Sul ponticello", "incorrect": ["Pizzicato", "Sul pontiv√©lla", "Bangtanio amazingo"]}, "20": {"question": "How many sections of violins are usually found in the symphony orchestra?", "correct": "Two", "incorrect": ["Three", "Four", "One"]}, "21": {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a way the Mozart is typical of the time period?", "correct": "Plays with formal conventions and expectations", "incorrect": ["Written in sonata form", "Uses Classical chamber music compositional techniques", "Development is in a related key"]}, "22": {"question": "What are the four movements of the complete Mozart?", "correct": "Fast movement, slow movement, minuet and trio, fast finale", "incorrect": ["Slow movement, minuet and trio, fast movement, fast finale", "There are three movements", "Minuet and trio, slow movement, fast movement, moderate finale"]}, "23": {"question": "Which is one of the expressive possibilities that the string quartet presented composers with?", "correct": "Greater subtleties than large-scale instrumental genres e.g. symphonies and concertos", "incorrect": ["Increased possibilities for tonal complexity, compared to large-scale instrumental genres", "Greater opportunities to feature J-Hope's rapping skills", "Less reliance on terrace dynamics, compared to solo works"]}, "24": {"question": "What is sonata form?", "correct": "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of three main sections: exposition, development and recapitulation.", "incorrect": ["A large-scale instrumental form consisting of three main sections: A, B, and A.", "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of two main sections: A and B.", "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of indefinite sections, in the order of A, B, A, C, A, D, A, E, et cetera."]}, "25": {"question": "Which of the following does the exposition NOT present?", "correct": "Tierce de Picardie", "incorrect": ["Thematic material", "Tonal contrast", "Modulating from the tonic to a related key (usually the dominant if the orgiinal key is major or the relative major if the original key is minor)"]}, "26": {"question": "Which of the following was NOT a composer of string quartets?", "correct": "John Dowland", "incorrect": ["Carl Dittersdorf", "Ludwig van Beethoven", "Johann Wanhal"]}, "27": {"question": "Mozart - What key does the piece modulate to for the development and what its relationship to the tonic key?", "correct": "D major, dominant", "incorrect": ["D major, subdominant", "E major, dominant", "B minor, relative minor"]}, "28": {"question": "Mozart - Which of the following is NOT part of the job of the development section?", "correct": "Repeat most of the exposition", "incorrect": ["Modulate through a range of keys", "Eventually go back to the tonic", "Work over' motifs and thematic material of the exposition e.g. through sequenes and dominant harmony."]}, "29": {"question": "Mozart - Which of the following is used in the B section (minor)?", "correct": "Augmented chords", "incorrect": ["Diatonic melody", "Slower tempo (langsam)", "Modulation"]}, "30": {"question": "Mozart - What does the 'K' in K. 387 mean?", "correct": "The catalogue of Mozart's works made by Ludwig von Kochel", "incorrect": ["The catalogue of Mozart's works made by Kai Huening", "The catalogue of Baroque works made by Ludwig von Kochel", "The catalogue of all classical works made by Ludwig von Kochel"]}, "31": {"question": "Mozart - What does the '387' in K. 387 mean?", "correct": "It is his 387th work, ordering chronologically", "incorrect": ["It is his 87th work in his 3rd decade", "It is his 387th work, ordering alphabetically", "It is his 378th work, ordering chronologically"]}, "32": {"question": "What does the term Allegro vivace assai mean?", "correct": "Fast and very lively", "incorrect": ["Very fast and very lively", "Very fast", "Brisk and lively"]}, "33": {"question": "Mozart: What period is the initial development of chamber music linked to?", "correct": "Classical Period", "incorrect": ["Baroque Period", "Romantic Period", "Jazz Period", "The 80's"]}, "34": {"question": "Mozart: What feature separates the string quartet from Baroque forms?", "correct": "Basso continuo", "incorrect": ["It requires a violin", "Its music is better", "Cheaper", "Its instrumentation is different"]}, "35": {"question": "Mozart: When did the first string quartets appear?", "correct": "In the 1760's", "incorrect": ["Stone Age", "In the 1800's", "In the 1780's", "Jesus time, brah"]}, "36": {"question": "Mozart: Where did the first string quartets appear?", "correct": "South Germany, Austria, Bohemia", "incorrect": ["In ur mum's basement", "China", "Germany and Bolivia", "New Orleans"]}, "37": {"question": "Mozart: To which socioeconomic group did this music appeal?", "correct": "Enlightened' upper classes", "incorrect": ["Poor lower classes", "Hard-working American taxpayers", "Poor upper classes", "Rich homeless people"]}, "38": {"question": "Mozart: How many players are required and what kind of space is it played in?", "correct": "4 players in a small space", "incorrect": ["4 players in a large space", "3 players in a small space", "5 players in a large space", "The entire population of the Asian continent (approximately 4.5 billion)"]}, "39": {"question": "Mozart: Where were the quartets composed and when?", "correct": "In Vienna, between 1782 and 1785", "incorrect": ["In ur mum's basement", "In Italy between 1782 and 1785", "Nazi Germany", "Germany in the early 1800's"]}, "40": {"question": "Mozart: How many of the quartets were composed?", "correct": "6", "incorrect": ["5", "1", "4", "1,000,000,000,000"]}, "41": {"question": "Mozart: Who were the set of quartets dedicated to?", "correct": "Haydn", "incorrect": ["Bach", "Mozart", "Beethoven", "Jesus"]}, "42": {"question": "Mozart: To which work(s) were the works written in response to?", "correct": "Haydn's Op. 33 set", "incorrect": ["Mozart's Op. 10 set", "Beethoven's Op. 28 set", "Haydn's Op. 34 set", "Baby shark"]}, "43": {"question": "Mozart: What are the four movements in this String quartet K 387?", "correct": "Fast movement, Slow movement, Minuet and trio, Fast finale", "incorrect": ["Fast movement, even faster movement, even more faster movement, a movement that's so fast you didn't even realise it was playing until it ended", "Fast movement, Slow movement, Fast movement, Slow movement", "Fast movement, fast movement, slow movement, minuet and trio", "Slow movement, slower movment, fast finale, minuet and trio"]}, "44": {"question": "Mozart: What are the two main archetypes of a theme in the Classical style?", "correct": "Sentence and period", "incorrect": ["Sentence and full stop", "Sentence and response", "Dark mode and light mode", "Syncopation", "Archetypes don't exist, conspiracy confirmed"]}, "45": {"question": "Mozart: What comprises a 'sentence' theme?", "correct": "A 'presentation' phrase then a 'continuation and cadential' phrase", "incorrect": ["A theme that sentences.", "A continuation phrase then a presentation of the results", "A basic idea then a repetition of the basic ideas", "Some words and then a full stop at the end."]}, "46": {"question": "Mozart: What does a presentation phrase comprise of?", "correct": "A two bar basic idea which is either repeated or modified", "incorrect": ["An eight bar basic idea thats repeated again so its 16 so thats quick maths", "A two bar idea followed by another two bar idea", "A four bar idea which is repeated", "A song thats topping the charts"]}, "47": {"question": "Mozart: How many parts does the development have?", "correct": "4", "incorrect": ["3", "5", "6", "As many as there are points in my IQ (in that case, none)"]}, "48": {"question": "Mozart: What type of theme does the first four bars of the exposition suggest?", "correct": "Period-type theme", "incorrect": ["Sentence theme", "Yellow theme", "Halloween theme", "Cadential theme"]}, "49": {"question": "Mozart: Instead of returning to the initial basic idea at bars 5 and 6, what does the melody do?", "correct": "Fragmentary process like the 'continuation' of the sentence type", "incorrect": ["A process called photosynthesis", "The melody exposes the material from the development", "It finishes in an imperfect cadence", "It votes for Biden"]}, "50": {"question": "Mozart: What kind of theme does this become?", "correct": "A kind of 'hybrid' theme of the period and sentence themes", "incorrect": ["A triple theme", "A period theme", "A sentence theme", "It doesn't"]}, "51": {"question": "Mozart: How many additional bars are added to the standard eight-bar structure at bar 1?", "correct": "2", "incorrect": ["4", "8", "1", "262"]}, "52": {"question": "Mozart: What are the two cadences that occur at bar 8 and bar 10?", "correct": "Interrupted and Perfect", "incorrect": ["Interrupted and Plagal ", "Plagal and Perfect ", "Pianist", "Imperfect and Perfect"]}, "53": {"question": "Mozart: In which bar does the transition begin?", "correct": "Bar 11", "incorrect": ["Bar 18", "Bar 1", "Bar 9", "Bar Mitzvah"]}, "54": {"question": "Mozart: In which parts is the basic idea restated then imitated?", "correct": "Second violin then first violin", "incorrect": ["First violin then second violin", "Second violin then third violin", "First violin then the baritone saxophone", "Upper North Shore"]}, "55": {"question": "Mozart: To where does the piece modulate to by bar 16?", "correct": "Dominant", "incorrect": ["Subdominant", "Tonic", "Leading Note", "Alabama"]}, "56": {"question": "Mozart: Which key is bars 21-24 in, and what does this create?", "correct": "D major, creating a drawn-out imperfect cadence in dominant key", "incorrect": ["G major, creating a perfect cadence", "F flat major, creating disharmony amongst the music community", "E major, creating contrast to the previous section", "It is in the key of C chromatic scale because that is what everything is in (massive brain moment)"]}, "57": {"question": "Mozart: What does Mozart play tricks on?", "correct": "Expectations of Classical thematic conventions", "incorrect": ["His unicycle", "His own mind, he was delusional", "Expectations of Jazz people", "Everyone and everything and everyone"]}, "58": {"question": "Mozart: How many extra bars are added to the standard eight-bar structure commencing at bar 25?", "correct": "6", "incorrect": ["4", "2", "1", "26"]}, "59": {"question": "Mozart: What does the repitition of the basic idea a step lower from bar 25 at bar 27 suggest?", "correct": "A sentence-type theme", "incorrect": ["A period theme", "Mozart was loony ", "It doesn't suggest anything, stop being so suspicious", "The basic idea was repeated a step lower"]}, "60": {"question": "Mozart: At bar 29, what would usually follow the repition of the basic idea?", "correct": "Fragmentation and continuation", "incorrect": ["Repitition", "Syncopation", "The basic idea", "Sentence and period"]}, "61": {"question": "Mozart: What happens at bar 29 instead?", "correct": "A two bar contrasting idea with a weak imperfect cadence", "incorrect": ["A similar idea with a perfect cadence", "A contrasting idea with an imperfect cadence", "The basic idea followed by a plagal cadence", "The basic idea is repeated in a different key"]}, "62": {"question": "Mozart: Which bars are the first and second subordinate themes?", "correct": "First is 25, second is 39", "incorrect": ["First is 39, second is 49", "They happen simultaneously", "First is at bar 40, second at 50", "Yellow submarine"]}, "63": {"question": "Mozart: What is the name of the totality of subordinate themes?", "correct": "Subordinate theme group", "incorrect": ["Subordinate themes", "Ordinate Subtheme group", "Total of subordinate themes", "It is themes of subdorndasdlfk"]}, "64": {"question": "Mozart: How does the second subordinate theme differr from the first subordinate theme?", "correct": "It is less distinctive, consisting of more 'generic' passage work", "incorrect": ["It is more distinctive, as it includes the original material while experimenting with it", "It stays quite similar", "It comes after the first subordinate theme", "It is less distinctive, consisting of very repetitve phrases"]}, "65": {"question": "Mozart: Nearing the end of the exposition, there is a reptitive harmonic motion, mainly through which chords?", "correct": "IV-V-I", "incorrect": ["I-V-vi", "V-VI-I", "I-IV-V", "ii-V-I"]}, "66": {"question": "Mozart: What kind of cadence occurs at bar 47?", "correct": "Interrupted", "incorrect": ["Plagal", "Imperfect", "Perfect", "Cadence constructions"]}, "67": {"question": "Mozart: What closes the second subordinate theme and where?", "correct": "A harmonic progression towards a perfect cadence at bar 49", "incorrect": ["A harmonic progression towards an imperfect cadence at bar 49", "A chromatic progression towards a perfect cadence at bar 39", "A ii-V-I progression at bar 49", "A harmonic progression towards a perfect cadence at bar 49"]}, "68": {"question": "Mozart: How many bars at the end of the exposition are included in the 'closing section'?", "correct": "6", "incorrect": ["All of them", "8", "4", "2"]}, "69": {"question": "Mozart: What usually comprises a closing sections?", "correct": "A series of cadence-like gestures (codettas)", "incorrect": ["Notes", "References to the basic idea from the opening", "A series of perfect cadences", "Dramatic phrasing"]}, "70": {"question": "Mozart: What is presented in the case of this closing section at the end of the exposition?", "correct": "Cadence-like gestures (marked by a and b)", "incorrect": ["Notes", "Chords from the development section", "Nothing (ladies and gentlemen, introducing - drum roll please - Mozart the rebel)", "Conclusive phrasing"]}, "71": {"question": "Mozart: Who is Joe?", "correct": "Joe mama", "incorrect": ["Joe Biden", "Joseph Stalin", "Joe's sandwich bar", "Joe (musician)"]}, "72": {"question": "Mozart: Where is the logical place to close the exposition?", "correct": "Bar 53", "incorrect": ["Bar 50", "Bar 55", "When the exposition starts because nobody wants to listen to it", "China"]}, "73": {"question": "Mozart: What is presented at bar 53 in the case of this piece?", "correct": "Also a cadential formula, but something entirely new and distinctive", "incorrect": ["Not a cadential formula, something entirely new and distinctive", "A cadential formula, with a closing perfect cadence that is completely to be expected", "A cadential progression that happens at the end of every exposition", "Global warming"]}, "74": {"question": "Mozart: What makes bars 54 and 55 distinctive?", "correct": "Dotted rhythms and total homophony", "incorrect": ["It is so polyphonic that you decide to become breatharian", "The articulative phrasing", "The notes don't fit the chords"]}, "75": {"question": "Mozart: What bar does the development start?", "correct": "56", "incorrect": ["65", "70", "1", "62"]}, "76": {"question": "Mozart: Part 1 of the development contains how many phrases?", "correct": "3", "incorrect": ["2", "4", "8", "17"]}, "77": {"question": "Mozart: What is the structure of each phrase in part 1 of the development?", "correct": "Motif x followed by a newly composed extension", "incorrect": ["Motif x followed by motif y", "Complete random structure where nobody has any idea what is happening", "A motif that is repeated", "Motif a followed by motif b followed by motif c followed by motif d etc."]}, "78": {"question": "Mozart: The first phrase of part 1 of the development places the motif + extension in which part?", "correct": "1st Violin", "incorrect": ["Viola", "Cello", "Saxophone", "2nd Violin"]}, "79": {"question": "Mozart: The second phrase of part 1 of the development places the motif + extension in which part?", "correct": "2nd Violin", "incorrect": ["Viola", "Cello", "Saxophone", "1st Violin"]}, "80": {"question": "Mozart: The third phrase of part 1 of the development places the motif + extension in which part?", "correct": "Viola", "incorrect": ["1st Violin", "2nd Violin", "3rd Violin", "Cello"]}, "81": {"question": "Mozart: Could Mozart shred", "correct": "Probably not", "incorrect": ["Absolutely", "Without a doubt", "Definitely", "Mhm"]}, "82": {"question": "Mozart: What key is the development mainly in?", "correct": "D major", "incorrect": ["A major", "G major", "D minor ", "Circular Quay"]}, "83": {"question": "Mozart: The first phrase of part 1 of the development does what harmonically?", "correct": "Commences in D major and concludes in E minor", "incorrect": ["Stays in D major", "Cycle of fifths progression towards C major", "Commences in D major and ends in A major", "Provides an opportunity for a bass solo"]}, "84": {"question": "Mozart: The second phrase of part 1 of the development does what harmonically?", "correct": "Moves through a circle of fifths progression toward C major", "incorrect": ["Remains in C major", "Commences in D major then moves to E minor", "Nothing, everyone just goes quiet and stares at the floor", "It searches for resolution in the tonic"]}, "85": {"question": "Mozart: The third phrase of part 1 of the development does what harmonically?", "correct": "Remains in C major", "incorrect": ["Remains in D major", "Commences in C major then moves to A minor", "Cycle of fifths progression towards the tonic, D major", "Moves to the dominant key, A major"]}, "86": {"question": "Mozart: How can the harmonic nature of the music be described at the first part of the devleopment section?", "correct": "Flexible", "incorrect": ["Consistent", "Boring", "Unpredictable", "Repetitive"]}, "87": {"question": "Mozart: What does the viola complete its thematic entry (motif + extension) with in phrase 3 of part 1 of the development?", "correct": "An unaccompanied flourish, which is a further extension", "incorrect": ["A phrase that fits a perfect cadence", "A phrase that fits an imperfect cadence", "Fragments of the basic idea", "A dessert"]}, "88": {"question": "Mozart: The viola's solo passage in the third phrase of part 1 of the development creates a model that is used where?", "correct": "The sequence for the commencement of part 2 of the devleopment", "incorrect": ["The sequence for the end of part 1 of the development", "At the end of part 2 of the development", "At the end of the development", "In a showroom"]}, "89": {"question": "Mozart: Where and what size is the model created by the viola's solo passage in the third phrase of part 1 of the development?", "correct": "A two bar unit in bars 72-73, heard another three times in sequence", "incorrect": ["A two bar unit in bars 70-71, heard another three times in sequence", "A four bar unit in bars 72-75, heard again in sequence", "A four bar unit in bars 70-73, heard another three times in sequence", "A 2 minute long model that outlines the points that the team will debate"]}, "90": {"question": "Mozart: The sequence that the viola's model in the third phrase of part 1 of the development is  played over what?", "correct": "Unresolved dominant 7th chords on a chromatically rising bass line", "incorrect": ["A harmonic progression of ii-V-I that continues with a bass line", "Unresolved diminished 7th chords on a chromatically rising bass line", "Imperfect and interrupted cadences ", "The double bass parts"]}, "91": {"question": "Mozart: How does the second part of the development constrast to the first?", "correct": "The second establishes a sense of purpose in constrast to the more exploratory and hesitant first part", "incorrect": ["The second part is in a different mode as opposed to the first one", "The second part is more hesitant as opposed to the first which has a sense of purpose", "More expressive techniques are used as opposed to the first part which lacks interest and variety", "It doesn't happen"]}, "92": {"question": "Mozart: What is often thought of as the core of the development?", "correct": "The moment of decisiveness (sequencing techniques following a less clearly directed part)", "incorrect": ["The new theme being introduced", "A hard seed, similar to a peach", "The basic idea from the exposition being developed", "The movement into a different key that is not the dominant"]}, "93": {"question": "Mozart: At which bar does the sequencing finish in part 2 of the development?", "correct": "Bar 80", "incorrect": ["Bar 82", "Bar 78", "Bar 1", "Bar 92.5"]}, "94": {"question": "Mozart: What key does the sequencing in part 2 of the development finish in and the development remain in?", "correct": "E minor", "incorrect": ["G major", "C major", "A minor", "H diminished"]}, "95": {"question": "Mozart: Which bars in part 2 of the development confirm the key and dissipate the syncopation?", "correct": "80-81", "incorrect": ["81-82", "82-83", "1-170", "80-83"]}, "96": {"question": "Mozart: What begins at bar 82?", "correct": "A new thematic unit", "incorrect": ["A new era for the American people", "The closing section of the exposition", "A new motif ", "The development"]}, "97": {"question": "Mozart: What does the second thematic unit of part 2 of the development comprise?", "correct": "A two bar unit", "incorrect": ["A four bar unit", "An eight bar unit", "A sixteen bar unit", "A one bar unit"]}, "98": {"question": "Mozart: In which part does the second two bar unit in part 2 of the development occur and how many times?", "correct": "First violin twice", "incorrect": ["Second violin once", "Second violin twice", "First violin once", "Viola twice"]}, "99": {"question": "Mozart: From where do bars 86-89 draw material?", "correct": "Closing section of the exposition, in particular motifs b and c ", "incorrect": ["The beginning of the development section", "The beginning of the exposition, especially motif a", "One of Mozart's other works", "From a quarry"]}, "100": {"question": "Mozart: What does part 3 of the development commence with?", "correct": "A new sequence with a one bar model ", "incorrect": ["A new sequence with a two bar model", "A bang", "Material from the closing section of the exposition", "A sense of purpose"]}, "101": {"question": "Mozart: In what bar does part 3 of the development begin?", "correct": "Bar 90", "incorrect": ["Bar 82", "Bar 88", "Bar 102", "Bar 92"]}, "102": {"question": "Mozart: By how much higher is each sequence than the model at the beginning of part 3 of the developement?", "correct": "A perfect fourth", "incorrect": ["A perfect fifth", "An octave", "A tone", "Out of the audible spectrum"]}, "103": {"question": "Mozart: The first two sequences in part 3 of the development express what cadence type?", "correct": "V7-I", "incorrect": ["IV-I", "I-V7", "vi-vii", "All of the above"]}, "104": {"question": "Mozart: What happens at bars 92-93 instead of the expected V7-I?", "correct": "V7-VI", "incorrect": ["Viola", "V7-I", "I-V7", "Vi7-vi"]}, "105": {"question": "Mozart: What key does the new theme in part 3 of the development work towards (at bars 93-97)?", "correct": "D major", "incorrect": ["A major", "B minor ", "C major", "All of the above"]}, "106": {"question": "Mozart: The exposition's closing section is heard again at bars 97-100, but it is in which key?", "correct": "D major", "incorrect": ["D minor", "A major", "B minor", "E major"]}, "107": {"question": "Mozart: What is part 4 of the development usually called?", "correct": "Retransition", "incorrect": ["Transition", "Closing section ", "End bit", "The end of an old life but the beginning of a new one"]}, "108": {"question": "Mozart: What happens in part 4 of the development harmonically?", "correct": "The dominant harmony in the tonic key is introduced", "incorrect": ["The subordinate melody in the tonic key is introduced", "The subordinate themes are repeated in the harmonic parts", "The dominant harmony in the dominant key is introduced", "It has a solo"]}, "109": {"question": "Mozart: What two kinds of variation to the exposition can be expected in the recapitulation?", "correct": "Decorative and Structural", "incorrect": ["Structural and Exploratory", "Decorative and Festive", "Notational and Structural", "All of the above"]}, "110": {"question": "Mozart: What are decorative changes?", "correct": "Variations to expression; no material change", "incorrect": ["Variations to material; no expressional change", "Setting up a Christmas tree", "Any substantially new or altered material", "Ornamentations and trills added for interest"]}, "111": {"question": "Mozart: What are structural changes?", "correct": "Any substantially new or altered material", "incorrect": ["Changes to the layout of the section", "Different ideas replacing the old ones", "Variations to expression; no material change", "Like when a banana is genetically edited to become a pineapple"]}, "112": {"question": "Mozart: The plan of the recapitulation is fairly similar to the plan of the exposition, except for what key difference?", "correct": "Everything is now in the tonic", "incorrect": ["Everything is now in the dominant", "Everything is now in a minor key", "The structure of them are completely different", "Its at the end instead of the beginning"]}, "113": {"question": "Mozart: What and where is the only difference in the main theme in the recapitulation?", "correct": "At bar 116, additional one-bar unit presented", "incorrect": ["At bar 118, additional one-bar unit presented", "At bar 116, additional two-bar unit presented", "At bar 120, additional four-bar unit presented", "There is no difference"]}, "114": {"question": "Mozart: What is the main alteration in the transition of the recapitulation?", "correct": "A structural change at bar 123, which allows the rest of the transition to be in the tonic key", "incorrect": ["A decorative change at bar 123, which allows the rest of the transition to be in the tonic key", "yeetus to the foetus", "A structural change at bar 125, which allows the rest of the transition to be in the tonic key", "The key is changed, meaning that the listener is thrown off"]}, "115": {"question": "Mozart: Are there any surprises in the first subordinate theme in the recapitulation?", "correct": "No", "incorrect": ["Yes", "Maybe", "None of the above because there is no such thing as a subordinate theme", "Definitely possible but no because everything is not possibly definite"]}, "116": {"question": "Mozart: Are there any surprises in the second subordinate theme in the recapitulation?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "None of the above because there is no such thing as a subordinate theme", "Definitely possible but possibly maybe because everything is not possibly definite"]}, "117": {"question": "Mozart: Does the closing section of the recapitulation differ from the closing section of the exposition and how?", "correct": "Yes, with some changes to octave reiger and two additional repeats of motive b", "incorrect": ["Yes, with some changes to the key and notation", "No it doesn't", "Yes, it contains different melodic ideas", "What's a closing section"]}, "118": {"question": "What is the lieder set work?", "correct": "Fruhlingstraum from Winterreise D. 911 by Schubert", "incorrect": ["Fruhlingstraum from Summerreise D.911 by Schubert", "Winterstraum from Fruhlingrreise D.911 by Schubert", "We Are Bulletproof : The Eternal by BTS (highly recommend)"]}, "119": {"question": "What does Fruhlingstraum mean?", "correct": "Dream of spring", "incorrect": ["Dream of summer", "Spring Day", "Dream of flowers"]}, "120": {"question": "What does Winterreise mean?", "correct": "Winter's journey", "incorrect": ["No More Dream", "Cold journey", "Lonely journey"]}, "121": {"question": "How many songs are in Winterreise and which number is Fruhlingstraum? (Respective)", "correct": "24, 11", "incorrect": ["14, 11", "34, 22", "24, 23"]}, "122": {"question": "What was a domestic factor in the development of the Romantic Lied?", "correct": "The growing availability and popularity of the piano and its presence in homes across a range of social classes.", "incorrect": ["The growing popularity of singing and availability of good teachers across a range of social classes.", "People's daughters transforming into ARMY fangirls, which led to composers panicking and introducing Romantic Lied.", "The decreasing popularity of Classical Lied among citizens which led composers to introduce Romantic Lied."]}, "123": {"question": "What was a factor in the development of Lied originally thought of by philosopher Johann Gottfried Herder?", "correct": "That language could unify all social classes, which sparked interest in lower classes.", "incorrect": ["That BTS would top the charts, so composers hurried to retain people's interest", "That music could unify all social classes, which sparked interest in lower classes.", "That language could only be appreciated by upper classes, which sparked an uprising in the lower classes."]}, "124": {"question": "Why did composers begin to focus on the piano accompaniment of Lieder?", "correct": "They realised the potential it had to support the text in a range of expressive ways.", "incorrect": ["They realised that it had previously had too great a role.", "They realised that BTS was too good at singing so they had to divert their attention to where they were not yet beaten.", "Their audiences were becoming dissatisfied with the piano part, so the composers had to adapt."]}, "125": {"question": "What is a song cycle?", "correct": "A unified collection of songs written to be performed in sequence.", "incorrect": ["A collection of songs written to be performed in a sequence of the performer's choice.", "A song with eleven unified parts to be performed in sequence. ", "A loop of the top ten BTS songs that plays ten times."]}, "126": {"question": "When was Winterreise composed?", "correct": "1828", "incorrect": ["1838", "1848", "1997"]}, "127": {"question": "Who wrote the poem Schubert set in Fruhlingstraum?", "correct": "Wilhelm Muller", "incorrect": ["Suga", "Wilfred Muller", "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe"]}, "128": {"question": "Schubert - What is a recurring idea in the text?", "correct": "The contrast between dreams and reality", "incorrect": ["The personalities of BTS members", "The contrast between love and loneliness", "The similarities between the narrator's past life and his dreams"]}, "129": {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a means through which composers unify song cycles?", "correct": "The songs are in the same time and key.", "incorrect": ["The songs are linked by explicit recollection of musical motifs between certain songs.", "There is often an implicit narrative thread.", "The songs are presented as musically independent numbers and the relationship is more implicit."]}, "130": {"question": "How does the changing music of Fruhlingstraum reflect its text?", "correct": "The 'happier' sections are symbolic of warmth and dreams, while the 'sadder' sections are symbolic of coldness and reality.", "incorrect": ["The slower sections are reflective of reminiscing dreams, while the faster sections reflect the poet's haste to focus on reality.", "The happier sections symbolise Schubert's love for Kpop, while the sadder sections convey Schubert's distaste for antis.", "The minor sections reflect the poet's old and harsh life, while the major sections reflect the great new life he has found."]}, "131": {"question": "What is the main subject matter of Winterreise?", "correct": "A poet who realises his destiny to always wander in solitude and perhaps never know love, companionship and rest.", "incorrect": ["A poet who must journey the world forever in search of something that does not exist.", "The hardships endured by BTS, which make international ARMYs sad because they can't help their oppas in Korea üò¢", "A wandering shepherd who is lost and cannot find his way home to his loved ones."]}, "132": {"question": "Comment on how Schubert treats the piano accompaniment in Fruhlingstraum.", "correct": "It imitates not only concrete imagery but evokes a feeling far more powerful than the text could.", "incorrect": ["It creates implicit imagery and imitates the feeling created by the text", "It is barely heard as Schubert intended for the voice to be the prominent part.", "It is the prominent part, bringing out the main imagery and themes in the piece."]}, "133": {"question": "How has Schubert set the six stanzas of poetry used in Fruhlingstraum?", "correct": "ABCABC", "incorrect": ["ABBCBB", "AABCCB", "ABACAA"]}, "134": {"question": "How is the music in Fruhlingstraum used to assist the story in Section A?", "correct": "Section A adopts a direct, folk song-like style with the help of the siciliana pattern which is associated with pastoral themes. The piano consists of gently rolling chords.", "incorrect": ["Section A adopts a direct, folk-like style with the help of the melisma pattern, associated with beautiful and floral themes", "Section A adopts a direct, folk song-like style with the help of the napolitana pattern which is associated with pastoral themes. The piano consists of gently rolling chords.", "Section A adopts a direct, folk song-like style with the help of the florentine pattern which is associated with pastoral themes. The piano consists of gently rolling chords."]}, "135": {"question": "How is the music in Fruhlingstraum used to assist the story in Section B?", "correct": "The tempo increases and the mode switches to minor. The piano consists of short, sharp block chords. ", "incorrect": ["The tempo decreases and the mode switches to minor. The piano consists of sharp, chromatic chords.", "The tempo increases and the mode switches to minor. The piano consists of harsh and fast rolling chords.", "The tempo increases and the mode switches to minor. The piano consists of gentle block chords."]}, "136": {"question": "How many lieder did Schubert write?", "correct": "Over 600", "incorrect": ["Over 60", "Over 6000", "Over 2013"]}, "137": {"question": "Schubert - What are the metric qualities of the verse?", "correct": "It is written in iambic trimeter (unstressed-stressed-unstressed)", "incorrect": ["It is written in iambic pentameter (unstressed-stressed)", "It is written in iambic pentameter (stressed-unstressed)", "It is written in iambic trimeter (stressed-unstressed-stressed)"]}, "138": {"question": "How is the structure of Fruhlingstraum effective as a narrative?", "correct": "Quatrains A are about the poet's dreams. Quatrains B are about his sudden awakening to reality. Quatrains C evoke the poet's yearning to return to his dreams.", "incorrect": ["Quatrains A are about reality. Quatrains B are about his unpleasant dreams. Quatrains C evoe the poet's yearning to return to reality.", "Quatrains A are about the poet's dreams. Quatrains B are about his sudden awakening to reality. Quatrains C evoke the poet's haste to flee his dreams.", "Quatrains A are about the poet's "]}, "139": {"question": "Which of the following does Schubert NOT use to effectively contrast the three ideas in Fruhlingstraum?", "correct": "Changes of instrumentation and texture", "incorrect": ["Changes of style", "Changes of modality and key", "Changes of tempo and meter"]}, "140": {"question": "What is the role of the piano in Lieder?", "correct": "It is an accompaniment of equal prominence to the text that supports the ideas and feelings of the text in expressive ways.", "incorrect": ["It is the prominent part, overpowering the text and expressively creating the main feelings and ideas.", "It is an accompaniment of less importance than the text that has little musical value, occasionally chipping in.", "It is a part of equal prominence to the voice and it introduces all the themes while the voice supports the ideas and feelings."]}, "141": {"question": "Schubert - What does the siciliana pattern found in the 4-bar introduction NOT present?", "correct": "Images of mountainous landscapes", "incorrect": ["Pastoral themes", "Images of nature", "Folk-like musical 'image' to the audience"]}, "142": {"question": "Schubert - What is the intention of the iambic trimeter used in the text?", "correct": "To promote a folk-like simplicity and 'artlessness' to the text", "incorrect": ["To demote a folk-like simplicity and 'artlessness' to the text", "To promote a delicacy and 'artfulness' to the text", "To promote images of sophistication for the audience"]}, "143": {"question": "Schubert - What is the final foot in the first line of each pair?", "correct": "An amphibrach", "incorrect": ["An iamb", "A reptibrach", "A trimeter", "A nudibranch"]}, "144": {"question": "Schubert - Do the main points of stress remain constant in the text?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Yes except for one instance", "Only for one instance"]}, "145": {"question": "What is a melisma?", "correct": "A group of notes sung to one syllable", "incorrect": ["A kind of rhythm associated with folkish, pastoral themes", "A term used to describe singing one note per syllable", "A pair of notes sung to one syllable"]}, "146": {"question": "Schubert - How is the setting of the text?", "correct": "Typical of Lied: it is mostly syllabic and the rare melismas occupy no more than 2 notes", "incorrect": ["Typical of Lied: it is rarely syllabic and melismas are found abundantly", "Untypical of Lied: it is rarely syllabic and almost every syllable is a melisma", "Typical of Lied: it is all syllabic."]}, "147": {"question": "Schubert - Which of the following is not represented by the major sections?", "correct": "Wealth", "incorrect": ["Dreaming", "Spring/warmth", "Love"]}, "148": {"question": "Schubert - Which of the following is not represented by the minor sections?", "correct": "Poverty", "incorrect": ["Reality", "Winter/coldness", "Loneliness"]}, "149": {"question": "Schubert - How is the material written?", "correct": "Almost completely diatonic without modulation", "incorrect": ["Almost completely chromatic with much modulation", "Almost completely diatonic with much modulation", "Very well "]}, "150": {"question": "Schubert - How does the piano foreshadow the singer's line?", "correct": "In the four-bar introduction by playing the melody in RH", "incorrect": ["In the four-bar introduction by playing the melody in LH", "In the eight-bar introduction by playing the melody in RH", "In the ten-bar introduction by playing the melody in RH"]}, "151": {"question": "Schubert - What is/are the predominant key(s) of the song?", "correct": "F major and F minor", "incorrect": ["E flat major and E flat minor", "G major and G minor", "D major and D minor"]}, "152": {"question": "Schubert - Which of the following keys are not used as [at least] brief modulations?", "correct": "D minor", "incorrect": ["C minor", "B flat major", "E flat minor"]}, "153": {"question": "Schubert - What does the 'D' in D.911 mean?", "correct": "The catalogue of Schubert's works made by Otto Deutsch", "incorrect": ["A form of cataloguing created by Ottoman Deutsch", "Dani :))", "The catalogue of Schubert's works made by Otto Dutch"]}, "154": {"question": "Schubert - What does the '911' in D.911 mean?", "correct": "It is his 911th work, ordering chronologically", "incorrect": ["Jet Fuel conspiracy theories.", "It is his 911th individual song/piece", "It is his 911th work, ordering alphabetically"]}, "155": {"question": "What does Schnell mean?", "correct": "Fast", "incorrect": ["Slow", "Very fast", "Not too fast"]}, "156": {"question": "What does Etwas bewegt mean?", "correct": "With some movement", "incorrect": ["With much movement", "With very little movement", "With no movement"]}, "157": {"question": "What does Langsam mean?", "correct": "Slow", "incorrect": ["Fast", "Not too slow", "Very slow"]}, "158": {"question": "Schubert - What keys were the song originally written in?", "correct": "A major and A minor", "incorrect": ["F major and F minor", "G major and G minor", "E flat major and E flat minor"]}, "159": {"question": "Schubert - Why was the song transposed?", "correct": "To suit a lower voice", "incorrect": ["To suit a higher voice", "Because they felt like it", "So it was more accessible to all voices"]}, "160": {"question": "Schubert - What is the meter of Stanzas A?", "correct": "6/8", "incorrect": ["2/4", "3/8", "3/4"]}, "161": {"question": "Schubert - What is the meter of Stanzas B?", "correct": "6/8", "incorrect": ["2/4", "3/8", "3/4"]}, "162": {"question": "Schubert - What is the meter of Stanzas C?", "correct": "2/4", "incorrect": ["6/8", "3/8", "3/4"]}, "163": {"question": "Schubert - What is the key of Stanzas A?", "correct": "F major", "incorrect": ["F minor", "E flat major", "G major"]}, "164": {"question": "Schubert - What is the key of Stanzas B?", "correct": "F minor", "incorrect": ["F major", "E flat minor", "E flat major"]}, "165": {"question": "Schubert - What is the key of Stanzas C?", "correct": "F major - F minor", "incorrect": ["E flat major - E flat minor", "G major - G minor"]}, "166": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the harmony of Stanzas A.", "correct": "Settled, diatonic, often using the tonic chord", "incorrect": ["Unsettled, chromatic, frequent key changes", "Sometimes irresolute (questioning)", "Settled, diatonic, rarely using the tonic chord"]}, "167": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the melodic style of Stanzas A.", "correct": "Flowing and carefree, often using the siciliana rhythm, with some rising leaps", "incorrect": ["Agitated repeated notes, rising semitones, wide leaps (mostly descending)", "Simple (mostly quavers, narrow pitch range) then sad (minor key, wider pitch range)", "Flowing and carefree, often using melismas, with few leaps"]}, "168": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the accompaniment of Stanzas A.", "correct": "Flowing broken chords in continuous triplet rhythm", "incorrect": ["Arpeggiated chords", "Throbbing chords and broken octaves", "Flowing block chords in continuous triplet rhythm"]}, "169": {"question": "How is Schubert's type of strophic form different from simple strophic form?", "correct": "Schubert uses the same music for each group of stanzas (1&4, 2&5, 3&6) rather than for every stanza", "incorrect": ["Schubert uses different music for each stanza", "Schubert uses the same music for each group of stanzas (1&2, 3&4, 5&6) rather than for every stanza", "Schubert uses the same music for each group of stanzas (1&2&3, 4&5&6) rather than for every stanza"]}, "170": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the harmony of Stanzas B.", "correct": "Unsettled, chromatic, frequent key changes", "incorrect": ["Settled, diatonic, often using the tonic chord", "Sometimes irresolute (questioning)", "Unsettled, chromatic, infrequent key changes"]}, "171": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the melodic style of Stanzas B.", "correct": "Agitated repeated notes, rising semitones, wide leaps (mostly descending)", "incorrect": ["Flowing and carefree, often using the siciliana rhythm, with some rising leaps", "Simple (mostly quavers, narrow pitch range) then sad (minor key, wider pitch range)", "Agitated repeated notes, rising semitones, narrow leaps (mostly descending)"]}, "172": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the accompaniment of Stanzas B.", "correct": "Throbbing chords and broken octaves", "incorrect": ["Arpeggiated chords", "Flowing broken chords in continuous triplet rhythm", "Detached block chords and octaves"]}, "173": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the harmony of Stanzas C.", "correct": "Sometimes irresolute (questioning)", "incorrect": ["Settled, diatonic, often using the tonic chord", "Unsettled, chromatic, frequent key changes", "Very resolute and unquestioning"]}, "174": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the melodic style of Stanzas C.", "correct": "Simple (mostly quavers, narrow pitch range) then sad (minor key, wider pitch range)", "incorrect": ["Agitated repeated notes, rising semitones, wide leaps (mostly descending)", "Flowing and carefree, often using the siciliana rhythm, with some rising leaps", "Sad (minor key, narrow pitch range) then simple (mostly quavers, wider pitch range)"]}, "175": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the accompaniment of Stanzas C.", "correct": "Arpeggiated chords", "incorrect": ["Flowing broken chords in continuous triplet rhythm", "Throbbing chords and broken octaves", "Block chords"]}, "176": {"question": "Schubert: What is the instrumentation of the piece?", "correct": "Voice and piano", "incorrect": ["Solo instrument and piano", "Orchestra", "String quartet", "Two pianos"]}, "177": {"question": "Schubert: What does Fr√ºhlingstraum mean?", "correct": "Spring dream", "incorrect": ["Winter dream", "Fruity Plum", "Violin", "Autumn dream"]}, "178": {"question": "Schubert: What kind of song is it?", "correct": "An art song", "incorrect": ["A pop song", "hell nah", "A sing song sang sung", "An instrumental song"]}, "179": {"question": "Schubert: What is D. 911", "correct": "Catalogue of his works", "incorrect": ["A random letter followed by a number", "Doomsday, 911 incident", "His 911th work", "A magazine catalogue"]}, "180": {"question": "Schubert: Who wrote the text for the work?", "correct": "Wilhelm M√ºller", "incorrect": ["J.K. Rowling", "Marcus Hildebrandt", "Leo", "Morenz Bittermann"]}, "181": {"question": "Schubert: What does Lied mean in German?", "correct": "Song", "incorrect": ["Piece", "Music", "Piano", "Past tense for 'lie'"]}, "182": {"question": "Schubert: How many songs are in the set called Winterreise?", "correct": "24", "incorrect": ["11", "16", "4", "911"]}, "183": {"question": "Schubert: In which place is Fr√ºhlingstraum in the set called Winterreise?", "correct": "11th", "incorrect": ["12th", "24th", "2nd", "DNF"]}, "184": {"question": "Schubert: What does Lied mean as a musical genre designation?", "correct": "A song set to German text", "incorrect": ["A song set to Italian text", "A piece of music with words", "Words with a piece of music", "A piece with words of music"]}, "185": {"question": "Schubert: How far back in time do Lied go?", "correct": "The Middle Ages", "incorrect": ["Jesus times", "The Renaissance", "The Dark Ages", "Prehistoric times (e.g. dinosaur)"]}, "186": {"question": "Schubert: In what time period did Lied develop to widespread recognition?", "correct": "The nineteenth century", "incorrect": ["Jesus times", "The eighteenth century", "10 minutes", "The seventeenth century"]}, "187": {"question": "Schubert: The devleopment of the Lied into widespread recognition had its roots where?", "correct": "The second half of the eighteenth century", "incorrect": ["The first half of the eighteenth century", "In the ground", "The second half of the seventeenth century", "The first half of the nineteenth century"]}, "188": {"question": "Schubert: What are the main reasons for the development of Lied into widespread recognition?", "correct": "The growth of German as a literary language, and how language can help social cohesion", "incorrect": ["The growth of Nazi Germany and Hitler's mo", "The growth of German as a literary language, and the development of Germany into a first-world nation", "The spread of European music across the world, and how language can help social cohesion", "Food from Germany becoming more popular around the world, and the love of their toilets"]}, "189": {"question": "Schubert: Who was at the forefront of the development of Lied into widespread recognition?", "correct": "Johann Wolfang von Goethe", "incorrect": ["Johann Sebastian Bach", "Heinrich Mitter", "Elmar Preiszner", "Ralf Reiter"]}, "190": {"question": "Schubert: What idea was developed by Johann Gottfried Herder?", "correct": "Language is the most powerful determinant of social cohesion", "incorrect": ["Music is the most powerful determinant of social cohesion", "The reason for the combination of music and language is that it sounds good", "That German food is tasty", "Language is the key tool of communication within a society"]}, "191": {"question": "What happened to Joe mama?", "correct": "They changed their last name to papa", "incorrect": ["They changed their last name to Biden", "Died in a hole R.I.P.", "Stopped practising saxophone so got spanked", "Joe"]}, "192": {"question": "Schubert: Whyy were peasants interested in Lied?", "correct": "The idea that Lied united everyone into one class", "incorrect": ["Lied gave them an opportunity to become rich performing it", "Lied let them understand what it was like to be in the upper class", "Peasants had a natural musical aptitude and therefore found it easier to learn and play", "They had nothing else to do"]}, "193": {"question": "Hello", "correct": "Goodbye", "incorrect": ["Die", "Why", "Hi", "Sigh"]}, "194": {"question": "Schubert: Why was much of the German poetry written in the early stages try to disconnect from the sophistication of the town/city?", "correct": "Town dominated by Italian opera, didn't want that style of music", "incorrect": ["Town dominated by Italian opera so they tried to rip it off outside of town", "The town was dominated by French opera, didn't want that style of music", "Town was dominated by German opera, but they didn't want that genre of music", "The sophistication of the urbanised areas did not suit the lifestyle of the peasants"]}, "195": {"question": "Schubert: The striving of German poetry during late 18th to early 19th Centuries toward oral folk traditions was for what purpose?", "correct": "People wanted an art that was unmediated by artificial formal conventions", "incorrect": ["People wanted music that had no connection to the music of the wealthy", "To revive folk music as it was very popular when it was around", "To remember and respect the ancestors of their music", "People wanted an art form that was not influenced by wealth or power"]}, "196": {"question": "Schubert: The urges for an art that was unmediated by artificial conventions (e.g. Italian opera) was amplified by what?", "correct": "The emerging Romantic movement", "incorrect": ["The emerging classical movement", "The emerging jazz movement", "Donald Trump's unwillingness to back down", "The emerging renaissance movement"]}, "197": {"question": "Schubert: What did the emerging Romantic movement emphasise?", "correct": "Unfettered expressions of feeling and emotion rather than the abstract appreciation of form", "incorrect": ["Undisturbed expressions of abstract appreciation of form rather than those of feeling and emotion", "The serious lack of aid provided by developed countries to developing countries", "Expressive techniques that were unique to the Romantic movement", "The emerging Romantic composers"]}, "198": {"question": "Schubert: What kind of feeling could this kind of music inspire in the individual?", "correct": "Feelings of the power of nature and awe and wonder", "incorrect": ["Feelings of the power of nature and resentment towards it", "Feelings of the weakness of nature and its dependence on humankind", "The awe and wonder inspired by a burrito", "How bad BTS is at making music (jk they don't make music)"]}, "199": {"question": "Schubert: What effect did the growing availability and popularity of the piano have on the development of the Romantic Lied?", "correct": "Led to the increasing numbers of German Lied being produced, due to presence in peoples' homes", "incorrect": ["Led to a serious shortage of piano teachers", "Led to a boom in the musical instrument manufacturing industry", "Led to the increasing numbers of German Lied being produced due to the lack of piano teachers", "Led to increasing numbers of home insurance claims due to the increased presence of pianos in peoples' homes"]}, "200": {"question": "Schubert: What caused composers to elevate the piano's role to support the text in Lied?", "correct": "The capacity for the piano to provide a level of inflection and subtlety not achievable on harpsichord", "incorrect": ["The capacity for the harpsichord to provide a level of inflection and subtelty not achievable on a piano", "The ability of the piano to play a variety of note durations and dynamics not achievable on a harpsichord", "The way the piano is able to play in a much larger range not achievable on harpsichord", "The ability to open the lid of the piano which is a cool function"]}, "201": {"question": "Schubert: Who was the first composer to realise the potential for a fusion of German poetic setting and sophisticated accompaniment", "correct": "Schubert", "incorrect": ["Mozart", "Bach", "Finzi", "Xi Jinping"]}, "202": {"question": "Schubert: How many Lieder did Schubert compose in his career?", "correct": "Over 600", "incorrect": ["Over 800", "Under 100", "Under 600", "Over 1000"]}, "203": {"question": "Schubert: How are song cycles unified?", "correct": "All the songs are composed by the same composer, words from same poet, and have references to a particular theme or tell the same story", "incorrect": ["All the songs were composed by the same composer but the words were from different poets, and the dynamics were the same", "The songs were composed by different composers and the words are composed by different poets, and the story is different", "A binder, maybe some paper clips or staples", "By recurring motifs and ideas, also by using the same modes/keys"]}, "204": {"question": "Schubert: Who was the first composer to link individual Lieder together into unified collections?`", "correct": "Beethoven", "incorrect": ["Mozart", "Finzi", "Schubert", "Xi Jinping"]}, "205": {"question": "Schubert: What was Beethoven's first song cycle?", "correct": "An die ferne Geliebte Op. 98", "incorrect": ["Seufzer eines Ungeliebten - Gegenliebe WoO 118", "Liederkreis, Op. 39", "Dichterliebe", "The Dark Side of the Moon, Op. Pink Floyd"]}, "206": {"question": "Schubert: How many different approaches to a song cycle emerged?", "correct": "Two", "incorrect": ["Three", "Four", "One", "Ten"]}, "207": {"question": "Schubert: What was Beethoven's approach to song-cycles?", "correct": "Link the songs  by explicit recollection of musical motives between certain of the individual numbers", "incorrect": ["Link the songs by using a consistent range of dynamics and expressive techniques throughout the songs", "Link the songs through the use of musical ideas that remained the same throughout every song", "Present the songs as musically independent numbers and allow the narrative relationship to be more implicit", "Link the songs as musically reliant variables on the dominant seventh dimished chord of the tonic mode major key"]}, "208": {"question": "Schubert: What was the non-Beethoven approach to song-cycles?", "correct": "Present the songs as musically indepenedent numbers and to allow the narrative relationship to be more implicit", "incorrect": ["Link the songs by explicit recollection of musical motifs between certain of the individual numbers", "Link the songs through the use of musical ideas that remained the same throughout every song", "Present the songs as musically dependent numbers and allow the narrative relationship to be more implicit", "Link the songs as musically reliant variables on the dominant seventh dimished chord of the tonic mode major key"]}, "209": {"question": "Schubert: Which approach to song cycles was favoured by Schubert?", "correct": "The non-Beethoven one", "incorrect": ["The Beethoven one", "Both of them, because Franz likes variety", "Neither, because he brought about a third style that was his own and more obscure", "The Mozart one"]}, "210": {"question": "Schubert: When was Winterreise composed?", "correct": "1828", "incorrect": ["1928", "1826", "1905", "2020"]}, "211": {"question": "Schubert: Did Wilhelm M√ºller consider the poems as a cycle?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "Probably", "Why not"]}, "212": {"question": "Schubert: In which perspective is the poem told from?", "correct": "First person", "incorrect": ["Second person", "Third person", "Fourth person", "Patient zero"]}, "213": {"question": "Schubert: How is the poet introduced in the set of poems?", "correct": "Leaving a village, passing the gate of his lost love he won in spring but has now lost", "incorrect": ["Leaving a village, passing the bakery at which he always used to buy bread from", "Entering a village, passing the gate of his lost love he won in spring but has not lost", "Leaving a village, passing his home where many memories were created", "Entering a village, smelling the delicious smells of baked bread and the pretty sights"]}, "214": {"question": "Schubert: In which sense is the poet on a journey?", "correct": "Physical and psychological", "incorrect": ["Physical and spiritual", "Spiritual and psychological", "Environmental and psychological", "Biological and psychological"]}, "215": {"question": "Schubert: What is an idea in the text that M√ºller constantly returns to?", "correct": "Constrast between illusion and reality", "incorrect": ["Contrast between Spring and Winter", "Contrast between walking and sitting", "Contrast between dreams and nightmares", "Contast between love and loneliness"]}, "216": {"question": "Schubert: What kind of attitude does the poet have?", "correct": "He is an outcast who will wander in solitude and never know companionship", "incorrect": ["He is highly likeable and will always have the companionship and love from others", "He is an outcast who will wander in companionship and love", "He is an extrovert who will wander in solitude and never know companionship", "He is an outcast who has many friends and his highly likebale"]}, "217": {"question": "Schubert: How is the higher awareness on the part of the poet expressed?", "correct": "He refers to the dreams of others and he knows the cold reality that awaits everyone", "incorrect": ["He refers to the dreams of higher beings and knows the cold reality that awaits everyone", "He refers to the dreams of others and he knows the pleasant reality that awaits everyone", "He refers to his own dreams and can see the future that awaits everyone", "The poet is able to see the cold reality that awaits everyone through his own dreams"]}, "218": {"question": "Schubert: What kind of rhyme scheme does Fr√ºhlingstraum have?", "correct": "abcabc", "incorrect": ["aabaac", "ababab", "abcdab", "aabbabababaaabbabababbabababbaababbabababababbababbab"]}, "219": {"question": "Schubert: What is the poet trying to promote in the text?", "correct": "A folk-like simplicity and artlessness", "incorrect": ["A folk-like complexity and artfulness", "The simplicity of the text", "A city-like complexity and thoughtfulness", "A city-like simpleness and artlessness"]}, "220": {"question": "Schubert: In some songs in the set Winterreise, the poet dreams himself, and awakens to a harsh reality. Is this the case in Fr√ºhlingstraum?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["Maybe", "I don't know, you tell me", "Most likely", "It is possible"]}, "221": {"question": "Schubert: How many quatrains does Fr√ºhlingstraum contain?", "correct": "6", "incorrect": ["8", "4", "2", "1"]}, "222": {"question": "Schubert: Each line in the poem comprises a loose what?", "correct": "Iambic trimeter", "incorrect": ["Iambic pentameter", "Grip on reality", "Iambic dimeter", "Iambic tetrameter"]}, "223": {"question": "Schubert: How can the poetic meter throughout the poem be described?", "correct": "Simple and consistent", "incorrect": ["Complex and irregular", "Complex and unpredictable", "Simple yet unpredictable", "Complex and consistent"]}, "224": {"question": "Schubert: How are the lines grouped?", "correct": "In pairs", "incorrect": ["In threes", "In fours", "In groups of ten thouSAND MILLION BILLION TRILLION GAZILLION", "Individually"]}, "225": {"question": "Schubert: How many metric feet are there in each line?", "correct": "Three", "incorrect": ["Two", "Four", "Seventeen", "Eleven thousand, nine hundred and eighty-four point three"]}, "226": {"question": "Schubert: What do the metric feet in most cases consist of?", "correct": "iambs (unstressed-stressed)", "incorrect": ["amphibrach (unstressed-stressed-unstressed)", "pyrrhic (unstressed-unstressed)", "dactyl (stressed-unstressed-unstressed)", "anapest (unstressed-unstressed-stressed)"]}, "227": {"question": "Schubert: In the first line of each pair, the final foot is what?", "correct": "amphibrach (unstressed-stressed-unstressed)", "incorrect": ["iambs (unstressed-stressed)", "pyrrhic (unstressed-unstressed)", "dactyl (stressed-unstressed-unstressed)", "anapest (unstressed-unstressed-stressed)"]}, "228": {"question": "What renders the metre loose rather than strict?", "correct": "Short additional syllables", "incorrect": ["Long additional syllables", "Medium-lenght additional syllables", "A shortage of syllables in some places", "A surplus of unnecessary syllables"]}, "229": {"question": "Schubert: Does the two-line metric preocess apply throughout the entire verse?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "Probably NOT", "Huh"]}, "230": {"question": "Schubert: What are melismas?", "correct": "A group of notes sung to one syllable", "incorrect": ["A group of syllables placed on one note", "A group of notes sung on a group of syllables", "A group of notes sung on two syllables", "A syllable sung on a note"]}, "231": {"question": "Schubert: What does syllabic mean?", "correct": "One syllable per note", "incorrect": ["Two sylllables per note", "Three syllables per note", "Two notes per syllable", "One syllable per three notes"]}, "232": {"question": "Schubert: What do the quatrains marked A (1 and 4) symbolise?", "correct": "Spring, birds and flowers, blossoming love", "incorrect": ["A quatrain", "Cold reality of WInter, harsh calls of birds", "Yearning to return to dream state, despair that is all illusion", "The harsh reality of the seasonal cycle"]}, "233": {"question": "Schubert: What do the quatrains marked B (2 and 5) symbolise?", "correct": "Cold reality of Winter, harsh calls of birds", "incorrect": ["Spring, birds and flowers, blossoming love", "A quatrain", "Yearning to return to dream state, despair that is all illusion", "The harsh reality of the seasonal cycle"]}, "234": {"question": "Schubert: What do the quatrains marked C (3 and 6) symbolise?", "correct": "Yearning to return to dream state, despair that all is illusion", "incorrect": ["Spring, birds and flowers, blossoming love", "Cold reality of Winter, harsh calls of birds", "A quatrain", "The harsh reality of the seasonal cycle"]}, "235": {"question": "Schubert: How many times does the poem cycle through the dream-reality-longing (ABC)?", "correct": "2", "incorrect": ["3", "1", "4", "So many times you're gonna lose count :)"]}, "236": {"question": "Schubert: What bars is Section A?", "correct": "1-14", "incorrect": ["15-26", "2-15", "26-44", "1-16"]}, "237": {"question": "Schubert: What bars is Section B?", "correct": "15-26", "incorrect": ["13-25", "44-43", "15-28", "1-14"]}, "238": {"question": "Schubert: What bars is Section C?", "correct": "27-44", "incorrect": ["15-26", "1-14", "25-44", "27-45"]}, "239": {"question": "Schubert: How does Schubert delineate the contrasts between the different sections?", "correct": "Changes of key/mode, tempo, style, metre", "incorrect": ["Changes of key/mode, dynamics, style, texture", "Change of dynamics and tempo but not expressive techniques", "Expressive techniques, dynamics, key/mode, tempo", "Style, mode, metre, dynamics"]}, "240": {"question": "Schubert: What do major modes represent in this song?", "correct": "Dreaming, spring, warmth, love", "incorrect": ["Reality, winter, coldness, loneliness", "Reality, summer, heat, companionship", "Dreaming, winter, warmth, loneliness", "Spring, coldness, loneliness, love"]}, "241": {"question": "Schubert: What do minor modes represent in this song?", "correct": "Reality, winter, coldness, loneliness", "incorrect": ["Dreaming, spring, warmth, love", "Reality, summer, heat, companionship", "Dreaming, winter, warmth, loneliness", "Spring, coldness, loneliness, love"]}, "242": {"question": "Schubert: Which section comes closest to adopting a direct, folk song-like style?", "correct": "Section A", "incorrect": ["Section B", "Section C ", "Section D", "Sections A and B"]}, "243": {"question": "Schubert: The material in section A is almost entirely...", "correct": "Diatonic", "incorrect": ["Chromatic", "Minor", "Gone", "Changed"]}, "244": {"question": "Schubert: The material in section A is cast in how many simple phrases?", "correct": "2", "incorrect": ["4", "6", "8", "1"]}, "245": {"question": "Schubert: What does etwas bewegt mean?", "correct": "With some movement", "incorrect": ["tgeweb sawte", "With patience", "With movement", "Slightly faster"]}, "246": {"question": "Schubert: How does the piano accompaniment foreshadow the singer's line in Section A?", "correct": "A brief four-bar introduction", "incorrect": ["A brief two-bar introduction", "A brief one-bar introduction", "A brief six-bar introduction", "A brief eighteen-bar introduction"]}, "247": {"question": "Schubert: What is siciliana?", "correct": "A slow musical style with lilting rhythms resembling a slow jig", "incorrect": ["A type of pizza", "A fast musical style with syncopated rhythms resembling a rondo", "A slow musical style with even rhythms resembling a waltz", "A fast musical style that has irregular rhythms resembling a six year old learning the piano"]}, "248": {"question": "Schubert: What kinds of themes are siciliana rhythms usually associated with?", "correct": "Nature and simple bucolic life", "incorrect": ["Buildings and complicated city life", "Nature and complex bucolic life", "Margherita, meat lovers, Hawaiian, pepperoni", "Simple country life and farms with cows"]}, "249": {"question": "Schubert: Where can a simple period be detected in Section A?", "correct": "Antecedent (bars 5-8) and consequent (bars 9-14)", "incorrect": ["Consequent (bars 5-8) and antecedent (bars 9-14)", "From bars 4-15", "Antecedent (bars 9-14) and consequent (bars 15-21)", "Antecedent (bars 6-9) and consequent (bars 10-15)"]}, "250": {"question": "Schubert: How does Section B contrast to Section A?", "correct": "Tempo increase, key change, mode becomes minor, accompaniment more staccato", "incorrect": ["Key change, mode becomes major, accompaniment more legato, tempo decrease", "Tempo increase, key change, mode becomes major, accompaniment more staccato", "Tempo decrase, key change, mode becomes minor, accompaniment more legato", "Tempo increase, key change, key becomes minor, accompaniment more staccato"]}, "251": {"question": "Schubert: What is sustained in the piano part by a tonic pedal in section B?", "correct": "A low tremolo", "incorrect": ["A high tremolo", "Basso continuo", "Slash chords", "An inappropriate accomapniment"]}, "252": {"question": "Schubert: What do the triplet figures marked x in section B act as?", "correct": "Jolts that destablise dream equilibrium", "incorrect": ["Jolts that reinforce the dream equilibrium", "Jolts that make the listener pee their pants", "Jolts that destablise the Winter reality", "Lead-ins to the next bars"]}, "253": {"question": "Schubert: What does schnell mean?", "correct": "Fast", "incorrect": ["Slow", "Walking", "Medium", "Speeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeed"]}, "254": {"question": "Schubert: What are augmented 6th chords?", "correct": "Chromatic chords which resolve to the dominant or sometimes the tonic", "incorrect": ["Chromatic chords which resolve to the tonic or sometimes the dominant", "The 6th is augmented (duh)", "Diatonic chords which resolve to the dominant or sometimes the tonic", "Diatonic chords which resolve to the tonic or sometimes the dominant"]}, "255": {"question": "Schubert: How are augmented 6th chords constructed?", "correct": "On the minor 6th degree of the scale and always include a note an augmented 6th above that", "incorrect": ["On the major 6th degree of the scale and always include a note an augmented 6th above that", "Intervals of minor 6ths piled on top of each other", "On the minor 6th degree of the scale and always include a note an augmented 2nd above that", "On the major 6th degree of hte scale and always include a note an augmented 2nd above that"]}, "256": {"question": "Schubert: The triplet figures marked x in section B involve inversions of what chord?", "correct": "The French augmented 6th chord", "incorrect": ["The German augmented 6th chord", "The Italian augmented 6th chord", "The French augmented 2nd chord", "The French suspended 6th chord"]}, "257": {"question": "Schubert: What is the Neopolitan 6th in bar 23?", "correct": "A supertonic triad constrcuted on the lowered 2nd degree", "incorrect": ["A supertonic triad constructed on the lowered 6th degree", "A supertonic triad constructed on the 5th degree", "A supertonic fourth constructed on the 5th degree of the 6th mode of the dominant 7th chord", "The 6th flavour of Neopolitan ice-cream"]}, "258": {"question": "Schubert: Does chromatic writing continue over the tonic pedal in bars 22-26?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "Possibly", "Probably"]}, "259": {"question": "Schubert: What feeling is created by the rapid modulation, chromatic harmony, minor-mode colouring and angular accompaniment in Section B?", "correct": "A powerful sense of disturbance, disorientation and distress - waking up from a dream", "incorrect": ["A powerful sense of reassurance, sleepiness and calmness - like falling asleep", "A powerful sense of disturbance, disorientation and distress - playing a note during a rest in an orchestra", "A powerful sense of disturbance, disorientation and distress - waking up from a dreamless sleep", "A powerful sense of reassurance, sleepiness and calmness - like eating chocolate"]}, "260": {"question": "Schubert: What does langsam mean?", "correct": "Slow", "incorrect": ["Fast", "Medium", "Turtle", "Speeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeed"]}, "261": {"question": "Schubert: What meter does Section C introduce?", "correct": "Simple duple", "incorrect": ["Simple triple", "Simple quadruple", "Compound duple", "Compound triple"]}, "262": {"question": "Schubert: What helps to set up a sense of stillness in section C after the agitation from section B?", "correct": "A new accompaniment pattern that remains quite constant", "incorrect": ["A new accompaniment pattern that varies a lot", "A reused accompaniment pattern that remains quite constant", "A new accompaniment that is constant in some parts and different in others", "An old accompaniment pattern that was drawn from a different song"]}, "263": {"question": "Schubert: The first two lines of text in Section C appear with a return to what key?", "correct": "The tonic major", "incorrect": ["The tonic minor", "The relative minor", "The dominant major", "The subdominant major"]}, "264": {"question": "Schubert: The first two lines in Section C are repeated, but what happens to the expected strong perfect cadence at bar 36?", "correct": "It is withheld", "incorrect": ["It is played as expected", "It is played and then repeated", "It is withheld and played two bars later", "It is played as unexpected, because they read the sheet music upside down"]}, "265": {"question": "Schubert: The arrival of the tonic in the bass is delayed until the final cadence in Section C, but what has changed regarding the mode?", "correct": "The mode is now minor", "incorrect": ["The mode is now major", "The mode is now diminished", "The mode is now dominant7", "The mode is now dark mode (iOS 14 feature)"]}, "266": {"question": "Schubert: How can the closure of Section C be described?", "correct": "Soaked with a feeling of loss and despair", "incorrect": ["Soaked with maple syrup like a pancake", "Soaked with a feeling of happiness and completion", "Soaked with a feeling of resentment and anger", "Epic"]}, "267": {"question": "What is the art song set work?", "correct": "O Mistress Mine from Let Us Garlands Bring Op.18 ", "incorrect": ["O Mistress Mine from Garlands Let Us Take Op.81 ", "Airplane, Pt.2 by BTS (highly recommend)", "O Mistress Mine from Let Us Bring Garlands Op.28 "]}, "268": {"question": "Who wrote the text of Let Us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Hitman Bang", "Milton", "Coleridge"]}, "269": {"question": "How many separate texts does Let Us Garlands Bring set?", "correct": "Five", "incorrect": ["Thirteen", "Eight", "Eleven"]}, "270": {"question": "Which of the following was NOT a composer of art song?", "correct": "[lieder composer]", "incorrect": ["Ralph Vaughan Williams", "John Ireland", "Arnold Bax"]}, "271": {"question": "What is O Mistress Mine about?", "correct": "It is a light-hearted reflection on love and youth.", "incorrect": ["It is a deep reflection on love and the mortality of youth.", "It is a light-hearted reflection on being grateful for little things.", "It is about waiting for 00:00 when the day will be over"]}, "272": {"question": "What was the 'English musical Renaissance'?", "correct": "The period in which England freed themselves from foreign musical influences, to have begun writing in a distinctively national manner", "incorrect": ["The period in which England freed themselves from old national English music and changed their style.", "The period in which English composers competed against BTS as to who could write better songs, and BTS won.", "The period in which England was overwhelmed by foreign musical influences and lost their national musical style."]}, "273": {"question": "Who wrote the art song set work?", "correct": "Gerald Finzi", "incorrect": ["Franz Schubert", "George Friedric Handel", "Rapmon"]}, "274": {"question": "What is the rhyme scheme of each sextain in Let Us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "AABCCB", "incorrect": ["ABACDC", "AAABBB", "ABBCBB"]}, "275": {"question": "Finzi - How are the modulations in the piece used to reflect the ideas in the text?", "correct": "The piece is bouncy as the poet addresses the object of his affection, and becomes more reflective as the poet addresses the need to be joyful while still young.", "incorrect": ["The song is determined as the idea of surviving one more day is expressed, and is temporarily taken back a notch as though building up energy to explode. ", "The piece is more reflective as the poet addresses the object of his affection, and becomes bouncy as the poet addresses the need to be joyful while still young.", "The piece is slow and melancholy as the poet addresses the once-was object of his affection, and becomes reflective as he addresses the need to be joyful while still young."]}, "276": {"question": "Finzi - What does the text consist of?", "correct": "Two six-line stanzas or sextains", "incorrect": ["Three six-line stanzas or sextains", "Six four-line stanzas or quatrains", "Hobicore vibes"]}, "277": {"question": "What is the role of the piano in O Mistress Mine?", "correct": "It sets up the general feeling in the introduction and remains remarkably consistent in mood, supporting the vocal part.", "incorrect": ["It is accompanied by the vocal part"]}, "278": {"question": "Which play is the text of Let Us Garlands Bring from?", "correct": "Twelfth Night by Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Twelfth Day by Shakespeare", "Ninth Night by Shakespeare", "Life Goes On by BTS"]}, "279": {"question": "Finzi - How is the vocal line?", "correct": "Simple and direct", "incorrect": ["Extravagant and indirect", "Excessively simple", "Straightfoward and monotonous"]}, "280": {"question": "Finzi - How is the text set?", "correct": "Syllabic and has a natural rhythm close to the declamation of the words.", "incorrect": ["Melismatic and has a rhythm not very close to the declamation of the words.", "Melismatic but has a natural rhythm close to the declamation of the words.", "Syllabic but has a rhythm not very close to the declamation of the words."]}, "281": {"question": "How does Finzi emphasise the point of the text?", "correct": "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the final line of each stanza", "incorrect": ["By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the final line of the piece", "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano of motifs throughout the piece", "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the first line of each stanza"]}, "282": {"question": "Finzi - What key does the harmony shift to at the final line of each stanza?", "correct": "The parallel minor", "incorrect": ["The dominant", "The relative minor", "The parallel major"]}, "283": {"question": "Finzi - What is the form of the song?", "correct": "Semi-strophic", "incorrect": ["Modified strophic", "Simple strophic", "Binary"]}, "284": {"question": "Finzi - What are the stanzas framed by?", "correct": "A piano inroduction, interlude and postlude", "incorrect": ["A piano introduction, interlude and voice+piano postlude", "A voice+piano introduction, interlude and postlude", "A voice introduction, voice+piano interlude, voice postlude"]}, "285": {"question": "Finzi - What key is the piece in?", "correct": "E flat major", "incorrect": ["A flat major", "E major", "F major"]}, "286": {"question": "What key does O Mistress Mine modulate to?", "correct": "It does not modulate", "incorrect": ["C minor", "The parallel minor", "G minor"]}, "287": {"question": "Finzi - How is the melody written?", "correct": "Mostly diatonic except for the end of each stanza where a modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["Mostly chromatic except for the end of each stanza where it becomes diatonic", "All diatonic", "Mostly diatonic except for the end of the piece where a modal mixture is introduced"]}, "288": {"question": "Finzi - What is the mood of the piece?", "correct": "Light-hearted and jaunty but becomes more reflective as modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["Reflective but becomes more light-hearted and jaunty as modal mixture is introduced", "Light-hearted and jaunty", "Reflective"]}, "289": {"question": "Which syllables does Finzi ensure land on the first beat of the bar?", "correct": "Stressed", "incorrect": ["Unstressed", "Both", "jUst rAndOm syLLaBLeS"]}, "290": {"question": "Finzi - Where are the only instances of direct imitation found?", "correct": "At the end of each stanza between the voice and the piano", "incorrect": ["At the beginning of each stanza between the voice and the piano", "There are no instances of direct imitation in the piece", "At the end of the piece between the voice and the piano"]}, "291": {"question": "Finzi - Describe the texture of the accompaniment at the end of the each stanza.", "correct": "Legato articulation and longer note values, slower pace, and dramatic contrast of dynamics.", "incorrect": ["Staccato articulation and shorter note values, faster pace, no contrast of dynamics.", "Legato articulation and longer note values, slower pace, less contrast of dynamics.", "Legato articulation and shorter note values, slower pace and dramatic contrast of dynamics."]}, "292": {"question": "Finzi - Describe the cadence at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "It is joined with the commencement of the next piano section (interlude/postlude)", "incorrect": ["It is separated from the next piano section (interlude/postlude)", "It is joined with the commencement of the next stanza", "It is joined with a four-bar outro of sorts before the interlude/postlude commences"]}, "293": {"question": "Finzi - In what way is the piece flexible and natural?", "correct": "The voice sets the text differently in each stanza while the accompaniment stays the same.", "incorrect": ["The accompaniment is different in each stanza while the voice stays the same.", "The voice sets the text differently in each stanza, just like the accompaniment.", "The voice and accompaniment stay the same, but rubato and ornaments are used."]}, "294": {"question": "Generally, what is the role of the Piano in Art songs?", "correct": "Shares prominence with the vocal part", "incorrect": ["Secondary to the vocal part", "Ternary to the vocal part", "Primary above the vocal part", "Quaternary to the vocal part"]}, "295": {"question": "Let us garlands bring is a set of how many songs?", "correct": "Five", "incorrect": ["Thirteen", "Eight", "Eleven"]}, "296": {"question": "What does Allegretto amabile mean?", "correct": "Moderately fast and pleasant", "incorrect": ["Not too fast and pleasant", "Very fast and unpleasant", "Walking pace and pleasant"]}, "297": {"question": "Finzi - Which of the following is NOT a stylistic characteristic of the song?", "correct": "Use of raised 7th notes in minor keys", "incorrect": ["Some dissonance and occasional use of parallel 5ths to the bass", "Irregular phrase lengths and syncopation and changes of meter", "Angular melodies (at times)"]}, "298": {"question": "What does sempre staccato mean?", "correct": "Always detached", "incorrect": ["Never detached", "The Ravenswood magazine", "Very detached"]}, "299": {"question": "Finzi - What key is the piano part in?", "correct": "E flat major", "incorrect": ["E flat minor", "A major", "A minor"]}, "300": {"question": "Which of the following techniques does Finzi NOT use in the song?", "correct": "Chromatic harmony", "incorrect": ["Imitation", "Counterpoint", "Diatonic harmony"]}, "301": {"question": "What kind of techniques does Finzi deliberately use in the song?", "correct": "Techniques associated with earlier music styles from Shakespeare's time", "incorrect": ["Techniques ahead of Finzi's time", "Techniques associated with earlier styles such as Classical", "Techniques associated with Kpop"]}, "302": {"question": "Finzi - What is the underlying message of the song?", "correct": "To seize life's joys and pleasures while you can", "incorrect": ["To be yourself", "To pursue your dreams", "To listen to BTS"]}, "303": {"question": "Finzi - Which of the following is NOT part of the change in texture at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "Faster", "incorrect": ["Broader", "Denser", "Slower"]}, "304": {"question": "Finzi - Who is the piece sung by?", "correct": "Feste, the jester in the court of Countess Olivia", "incorrect": ["Countess Olivia, to her jester, Feste", "Feste, the brother of Countess Olivia", "Feste, the father of Countess Olivia"]}, "305": {"question": "Finzi: What kind of song is this?", "correct": "An English art song", "incorrect": ["A Lied", "A pop song", "An instrumental song", "A British art song"]}, "306": {"question": "Finzi: How far back does the genre English art song go?", "correct": "Late sixteenth to early seventeenth centuries", "incorrect": ["Late seventeenth to early eighteenth centuries", "Late sixteenth to early eighteenth centuries", "Late fifteenth to early sixteenth centuries", "Back in my day"]}, "307": {"question": "Finzi: Lute songs by which composers are notable from the late sixteenth to early seventeenth centuries?", "correct": "John Dowland and Thomas Campion", "incorrect": ["John Dowland and Henry Purcell", "Ralph Vaughan Williams and Henry Purcell", "Michael Jackson and Thomas Campion", "John Dowland and William Walton"]}, "308": {"question": "Finzi: Whose works marked a high point in seventeenth century English music across all genres?", "correct": "Henry Purcell", "incorrect": ["Ralph Vaughan Williams", "Thomas Campion", "Arnold Bax", "Barack Obama"]}, "309": {"question": "Finzi: How did foreign influences come to dominate the musical landscape in England?", "correct": "The importation of Italian opera and in the works of Handel", "incorrect": ["Uncontrolled immigration", "Work opportunities attracting foreigners to England", "Serious self-esteem issues on the part of English composers (most of which fell into a deep depression)", "Their music was more appealing to audiences in England"]}, "310": {"question": "Finzi: The solo songs in England were dominantly developing where?", "correct": "From outside of England", "incorrect": ["In England", "Oceania", "Asia", "The Americas"]}, "311": {"question": "Finzi: The German tradition of the Lied was a large influence on the English art song. Which composers were part of that genre?", "correct": "Franz Schubert, Robert Schumann, Felix Mendelssohn, Johannes Brahms", "incorrect": ["Robert Schumman, Johannes Brahms, Johann Sebastian Bach, Franz Schubert", "Felix Mendehlssohn, Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, Johann Wolfgang Beethoven, Robert Schumann", "Franz Schubert, Roberto Schumann, Felix Mendelssohn, Johann's Bras", "Franz Schubert, Felix Mendelssohn, Johannes Brahms, William Shakespeare"]}, "312": {"question": "Finzi: What factors led to a period termed by some as the 'English musical Renaissance'?", "correct": "A growing sense of national awareness amongst English musicians, supported by a folk-song revival movement", "incorrect": ["A growing sense of national identity and confidence amongst musicians in England", "An increase in English composers in England at the time creating more music", "Foreign composers claiming to be English immigrating to England and composing masterpieces", "A growing sense of national awareness that encouraged people to write less music"]}, "313": {"question": "Finzi: What kinds of music were rediscovered in the 'English musical Renaissance'?", "correct": " 'Pre-Handelian' English music (court music) and British folk music", "incorrect": ["Jazz music, especially the elevator variety", "British folk music and renaissance music", "Renaissance music and 'Pre-Handelian' English music (court music)", "Pre-Bachian' English music and British folk music"]}, "314": {"question": "Finzi: Examples of twentieth century composers that were beneficiaries of the re-emergence of English music after foreign domination:", "correct": "Ralph Vaughan Williams, John Ireland, Arnold Bax, William Walton, Benjamin Britten", "incorrect": ["John Ireland, Benjamin Britten, Franz Schubert, Mark Walton, Arnold Bax", "William Walton, Ralph Vaughan Williams, Henry Purcell, Benjamin Britten, Arnold Bax", "Ralph Vaughan Williams, John Coltrane, Arnold Bax, Benjamin Britten, Miles Davis", "Ralph Vaughan Williams, John England, Arnold Bax, William Waton, Benjamin Britain"]}, "315": {"question": "Finzi: Examples of important English poets whose texts were set to music include:", "correct": "Shakespeare, Milton, Wordsworth, Coleridge, Hardy", "incorrect": ["Shakespeare, Dickens, Coleridge, Hardy, Wordsworth", "Keats, Milton, Shakespeare, Donne, Wordsworth", "Blake, Wordsworth, Hardy, Keats, Shakespeare", "John Lennon, Paul McCartney, Ringo Starr, George Harrison"]}, "316": {"question": "Finzi: What instrumentation is an art song comprised of?", "correct": "Solo voice and instrumental accompaniment", "incorrect": ["String orchestra and soloist", "Solo voice", "Solo instrument and instrumental accompaniment", "A chamber choir with a string quartet"]}, "317": {"question": "Finzi: How many short cycles of songs did Finzi compose?", "correct": "At least 8", "incorrect": ["8", "At least 24", "10", "16"]}, "318": {"question": "Finzi: From which English poet is Finzi's Let us garlands bring's text from?", "correct": "Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Coleridge", "Hardy", "Milhouse", "Wordsworth"]}, "319": {"question": "Finzi: Which of Shakespeare's plays is O mistress mine from?", "correct": "Twelfth Night", "incorrect": ["Macbeth", "Romeo and Juliet", "A Midsummer Night's Dream", "Hamlet"]}, "320": {"question": "Finzi: How many six-line stanzas (sextains) are there in the text?", "correct": "2", "incorrect": ["4", "6", "17.3", "8"]}, "321": {"question": "Finzi: What kind of rhyme scheme do the sextains have?", "correct": "aabccb", "incorrect": ["abacad", "x", "ababab", "abcabc"]}, "322": {"question": "Finzi: How is the form of the song best described?", "correct": "Semi-strophic", "incorrect": ["Strophic", "Through-composed", "Sonata form", "Binary form"]}, "323": {"question": "Finzi: What happens to the cadence at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "It is elided with the commencement of the next piano section", "incorrect": ["It is replaced with a sequence that leads to the commencement of the next piano section", "It is an imperfect cadence which leads nicely to the next section", "It is repeated except changed so it becomes a 'second go'", "The performer forgets about it because they have a mental blank and can't remember how to play their instrument"]}, "324": {"question": "What is a strophic song?", "correct": "Each stanza is set to the same music", "incorrect": ["No substantial repitition of music for each stanza", "A song without words", "A song with a very repetitive melody", "A song with a very repetitive harmony"]}, "325": {"question": "What is a through-composed song?", "correct": "No substantial repitition of music for each stanza", "incorrect": ["Each stanza is set to the same music", "A song without words", "A very thoroughly composed piece of music", "A song that has little to no repitition in it"]}, "326": {"question": "What is a semi-strophic song?", "correct": "Between strophic and through-composed, bit of the same music but also different in each stanza", "incorrect": ["A shorter strophic song", "A song with motifs and ideas that seem to match each other but are not the same", "A song with a repetitive melody that sometimes introduces new ideas", "A song that has verses that are the same as each other"]}, "327": {"question": "Where would the music be the same usually in a semi-strophic song?", "correct": "At the beginning of each stanza, being the most logical way to express identity", "incorrect": ["At the end of each stanza, being the best way to finish", "In the middle of each stanza because that is where the listener feels secure and understands the music", "At the beginning of the first stanza and the end of the second stanza", "At the end of the first stanza and the beginning of the second stanza"]}, "328": {"question": "Finzi: Which other composers have used this same text from Twelfth Night?", "correct": "Thomas Morley, Sullivan, Vaughan Williams, Charles Villers Stanford, Margaret Sutherland", "incorrect": ["Thomas Morley, Charles Dickens, Vaughan Williams, Margaret Sutherland", "Donald Trump, Vaughan Williams, Charles Villers Stanford, Sullivan, Thomas Morley", "Vaughan Williams, Shakespeare, Sullivan, Thomas Morley, Rudy Giuliani, Margaret Sutherland", "Purcell, Sullivan, Margaret Sutherland, Finzi, Thomas Morley"]}, "329": {"question": "Finzi: What key is O mistress mine in?", "correct": "Eb major", "incorrect": ["Bb major", "E major", "C minor", "Db major"]}, "330": {"question": "Finzi: Does O mistress mine ever modulate to another key?", "correct": "No", "incorrect": ["Yes", "Yes, to all 7 billion of them", "Nothing is impossible if you put your mind to it", "Definitely"]}, "331": {"question": "Finzi: How can the mood throughout most of the song be described?", "correct": "Light-hearted and jaunty", "incorrect": ["Dysphoric and delusional", "Anxious and irritable", "Cheerful and bright", "Melancholic and reflective"]}, "332": {"question": "Finzi: O mistress mine is mostly diatonic except for where?", "correct": "The final bars of each stanza where modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["The opening bars of each stanza where the ideas are being introduced", "The middle of each stanza", "The bridges between the stanzas", "China because they banned the import of diatonic"]}, "333": {"question": "Finzi: Where does the mood change to become more reflective?", "correct": "At the end of each stanza with the modal mixture", "incorrect": ["At the beginning of each stanza", "At the beginning and the end of each stanza", "When it nears the end of its life", "In the middle of each stanza to add an element of surprise"]}, "334": {"question": "Finzi: What does the right hand primarily consist of?", "correct": "A free, two-part texture with occasional thickening", "incorrect": ["A free, three-part texture with occasional thinning", "A free flowing melody that occasionally thickens", "A restricted, two-part texture with occasional thickening", "Five fingers and a palm"]}, "335": {"question": "Finzi: What does the left hand primarily consist of?", "correct": "A staccato 'vamping' accompaniment", "incorrect": ["A staccato unpredictable accompaniment", "Long sustained notes from the chords", "A walking bass line", "A free flowing countermelody"]}, "336": {"question": "Finzi: What is a consistent feature present in the left hand accompaniment?", "correct": "A downward stepping motion from the second beat of the bar to the first beat of next bar", "incorrect": ["An upward stepping motion from the second beat of the bar to the first beat of the next bar", "A downward stepping motion from the first to the second beat of the bar", "Dominant tenths", "An upward stepping motion from the first to the second beat of the bar"]}, "337": {"question": "Finzi: How do the interlude and hte postlude compare to the introduction?", "correct": "They are quite similar", "incorrect": ["They substantially differ as they share no common music", "They are identical", "They are not related to each other in any way", "They are much shorter, but make up for it in dynamics"]}, "338": {"question": "Finzi: Are the musical material from the vocal line and the piano part dependent on each other?", "correct": "No they are relatively independent", "incorrect": ["Yes because they constantly imitate each other", "Yes due to how the parts interlock and play together", "No but they do share a lot of the same ideas, so actually yes", "Yes because they are both in a sticky financial situation due to the Coronavirus pandemic"]}, "339": {"question": "Finzi: What type of text setting is the text?", "correct": "Syllabic", "incorrect": ["Neumatic", "Melismatic", "Problematic", "Dolichocephalic"]}, "340": {"question": "Finzi: What is accountable for the subtle rhythm changes from stanza to stanza?", "correct": "Natural declamation", "incorrect": ["Rubato", "Natural tempo variation", "Natural emphasisation", "The incapable musician not being able to tap their foot"]}, "341": {"question": "Finzi: How do the first lines of each stanza compare rhythmically?", "correct": "Different in their natural speech rhythms and have a different number of syllables", "incorrect": ["They are the same", "They share some rhythmic groupings", "Different number of syllables but similar speech rhythms", "Different in their natural speech rhythms but same number of syllables"]}, "342": {"question": "Finzi: How does the piano accompaniment for the first lines of each stanza compare?", "correct": "It is identical", "incorrect": ["They are in different keys", "They are at different tempos", "They are similar with a few note changes", "The piano isn't playing at that part, get pranked Laugh Out LOUD"]}, "343": {"question": "Finzi: Does the highly flexible, natural text setting remain consistent throughout the song?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "Possibly", "Naaaaaaaaaaah"]}, "344": {"question": "Finzi: At what points in the stanzas are the piano accompaniment and the melody similar?", "correct": "At the beginning and nearing the end", "incorrect": ["In the middle of both stanzas", "In the final line of both stanzas", "At the beginning of both stanzas", "Nowhere, because its a circle"]}, "345": {"question": "Finzi: Where is the only instance of direct imitation between the voice and the piano found?", "correct": "At the very final line in each stanza", "incorrect": ["The first line of each stanza", "The middle of the second stanza", "At the end of the song", "The beginning of the final stanza"]}, "346": {"question": "Finzi: What changes occur in the final two lines in each stanza?", "correct": "Harmony shifts to parallel minor, accompaniment texture changes, pace slows, dramatic dynamic contrast", "incorrect": ["Harmony shifts to parallel minor, pace quickens, overall texture becomes more dense and dynamics increase", "Harmony shifts up a major fifth, pace slows, accompaniment texture changes, dynamic contrast", "Pace quickens, accompaniment texture thins, pace slows, dynamics dramatically softer", "Nothing is changed here"]}}